<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Usage on Slides as Code</title><link>https://sacproj.github.io/documentation/usage/</link><description>Recent content in Usage on Slides as Code</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://sacproj.github.io/documentation/usage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://sacproj.github.io/documentation/usage/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sacproj.github.io/documentation/usage/getting-started/</guid><description>This page tells you how to get started with Slides as Code CLI and theme, including installation and basic usage.
Command Line CLI Installation Installation Requirements Homebrew Tarball Checking Installation CLI in Container Image Theme Installation Create new Presentation Code your Presentation Slides Homebrew as package manager Since Homebrew decided to merge Linuxbrew into Homebrew (see related blog post), in my opinion, with Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL), HomeBrew becomes a de facto multi-platform package manager.</description></item><item><title>Content Source</title><link>https://sacproj.github.io/documentation/usage/content/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sacproj.github.io/documentation/usage/content/</guid><description>Content file Content Format Content Source and Rendering Slides delimiters Speaker Notes Content file A content file is composed by 2 main components:
Front matter using YAML format delimited by ---. Content using Markdown, Shortcodes and CSS classes to describe the content. Content Format Hugo ❤️ Markdown (see Markdown page), but there are times when Markdown falls short.</description></item><item><title>Markdown</title><link>https://sacproj.github.io/documentation/usage/markdown/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sacproj.github.io/documentation/usage/markdown/</guid><description>Introduction Element Attributes Slide Attributes Tips &amp;amp; Tricks Introduction Slides as Code is a Hugo theme that uses Markdown and Shortcodes to implement slides content. Slides as Code doesn&amp;rsquo;t use Hugo&amp;rsquo;s Markdown renderer, but Reveal.js Markdown renderer called marked.
Thereby, Slides As Code is supporting GitHub Flavored Markdown, see Guide and Reference for further information.
On top of marked, Reveal.</description></item><item><title>Customization</title><link>https://sacproj.github.io/documentation/usage/custom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sacproj.github.io/documentation/usage/custom/</guid><description>Base Theme Theme Hugo Template and Configuration Contents VS Code Snippets ACME Theme Example Hugo Template, Configuration Contents VS Code Snippets Usage Base Theme sac-theme is a Base Theme of Slides as Code.
Theme Hugo Template and Configuration, VS Code Snippets and Contents are the composable parts of the Base Theme.</description></item></channel></rss>